A Guide to the McHone Brothers (LLC) Collection of Houck Tannery Records, 1870-1913: SC 0172
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Series 4: Distribution and Transportation Documents, 1893-1913
  - Time reports, Little River and Loose Tract, 1906-1908 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Time reports, Stokesville, 1906-1908 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Time reports, Miscellaneous statements and reports, 1906-1908 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Series 5: J.P. Houck Store, 1898-1912
  Series 5, J.P. Houck Store, 1898-1912, consists of materials that can be attributed specifically to transactions pertaining to the J.P. Houck Store, such as bills of lading for wholesale goods, customer charges, and freight and shipping receipts. These are arranged topically, then chronologically. The bulk of this series contains bills of lading for goods shipped to the Store [non-Virginia bills of lading], and bills of lading for goods shipped from the Houck Store to other locations in Virginia [Virginia bills of lading]. These are arranged by railway/company.
  - Bills of Lading [Non-Virginia], B&O Railroad Company, April 1898-1905 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Bills of Lading [Non-Virginia], B&O Railroad Company, 1906 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Bills of Lading [Non-Virginia], B&O Railroad Company, January 1907-July 1907, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Bills of Lading [Non-Virginia], B&O Southwestern Railroad Company, December 1901-1904 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Bills of Lading [Non-Virginia], Chicago Great Western Railway, July 1905-April 1906 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Bills of Lading [Non-Virginia], Pennsylvania Railroad Co., March 1902-February 1907 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Bills of Lading [Non-Virginia], Seaboard Airline Railway, September 1902-September 1904 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Bills of Lading [Non-Virginia], Southern Railway Company, August 1900-September 1911 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Bills of Lading [Non-Virginia], United States Express Company, December 1901-October 1903 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Bills of Lading [Non-Virginia], Miscellaneous Railroads, 1902-1912 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Bills of Lading [Virginia], Adams Express Company, December 1901-November 1908 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Bills of Lading [Virginia], Miscellaneous Railroads, 1902-1911 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Charge tickets, May 1908-January 1911 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Freight and Shipping Receipts, 1901-1902 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Freight and Shipping Receipts, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Freight and Shipping Receipts, 1904 (Box 7, Folder 35)